Fiary Choerudin

■ +628 1222 790 896 | Malo@fiqrychoerudin.dev | Digithub.com/fiqryq | Dilinkedin.com/in/fiqrychoerudin

Personal Profile

I am a software developer from Bandung Indonesia currently working as Frontend engineer for 2 years. i am working on react environment and use Typescript as my primary programming language and also love Tailwind for my CSS Framework.

Education

Telkom University Bandung, ID

Diploma Informatic Enginering

Aug 2017 - Aug 2020

- · Head of Multimedia Labolatory Research
- · Graduate with GPA 3.38

Work Experience

Kitabisa Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend Developer

May 2022 - Present

- Working with campaigner squad to develop features related to the campaign.
- Develop an internal product library called KBPL and already published some components like image, bottomsheet, chips, and menu navigation.
- · Develop revamp campaign detail especially fund detail.
- Technical Skills: Typescript, Javascript, ReactJs, NextJS, Git, TailwindCss
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

PUTI - Telkom University Bandung, Indonesia

Frontend Developer

Mar 2021 - Apr 2022

- · Working on an internal project for the international office app for managing student permits its called permit service.
- · Contribute to work on an application project to manage the certification of Telkom University employees and students called DigiTrain.
- · Develop dashboard portal data for academic Telkom university.
- **Technical Skills:** Typescript, Javascript, ReactJs, AngularJS, Git, SCSS, Bootstrap.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

Vallet Bandung, Indonesia

Internship Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

· Manage assets images at vallet app.

- Take image assets for publish on vallet app.
- Make assets like poster, banner etc.
- Technical Skills: Photoshop. Vallet app (design tools), Photography.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication.

Inovasi Semesta Ilmu (INOSI)

Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2018 - Feb 2018

- Develop augmented reality virtual tour Bandung.
- Technical Skills: C#, Unity 3D.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication.

Skills

Internship

Javascript, Typescript, Nodejs, Vanila CSS, Tailwind Css, NextJs **Programming**

Miscellaneous Linux, Git, Markdown.

> **Soft Skills** Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation.

Achievements:

Kitabisa Hackaton (Social Safety Nets Theme), Favourite champion

Jakarta

Languages _____

English Professional proficiency

Indonesia Native

OCTOBER 19, 2022